Nirenstein National Realty Map Company Records
© 2006 University of Connecticut
- Series III: Realty Records, undated, 1914-1980
  - Realty Correspondence
    - Valuation of West Street, 1960 (Box 16:791)
    - Winnie Service Station, 1949-1960 (Box 16:792)
    - Pratt and Trumbull Street properties, undated (Box 16:793)
    - Sumner Avenue property, 1961 (Box 16:794)
    - Wilmington, Delaware property, 1961 (Box 16:795)
    - Expense sheets, 1948-1950 (Box 16:796)
    - 63 Market Street property, 1949-1952 (Box 16:797)
    - Bowles Lunch Company, 1948-1950 (Box 16:798)
    - 161 Dwight Street property, 1961-1962 (Box 16:799)
    - Worcester, Massachusetts, Federal Savings and Loan appraisal, 1963 (Box 16:800)
    - Chestnut Street property sale, 1965-1967 (Box 16:801)
    - Nathan Nirenstein's appraisal qualifications, 1962 (Box 16:802)
    - Appraisal of the Republican Building, 1962 (Box 16:803)
    - Carlisle Hardware Company, 1956-1960 (Box 16:804)
    - Kellogg Building rents, 1970 (Box 16:805)
    - Real estate proposals and contracts, 1960-1962 (Box 16:806)
    - Report on incompleted theater building, 1928-1930 (Box 16:807)
    - General correpondence, A-Z, 1950-1972 (Box 16:808-817)
  - Realty Legal Documents
    - Amendments, 1962-1965 (Box 17:818)
    - Agreements, 1915-1965 (Box 17:819-821)
    - Bills of sale, 1959-1971 (Box 17:822)
    - Broker's license, 1968-1969 (Box 17:823)
    - Charter, 1929 (Box 17:824)
    - Contracts, 1923-1960 (Box 17:825)
    - Declaration of trust, 1956 (Box 17:826)
    - Deeds, 1914-1962 (Box 17:827)
    - Inventory of the estate of Henry L. Bowles, 1932 (Box 17:828)
    - Jury list, Kennedy case, undated (Box 17:829)
    - Justice McCook's decision in the New York Kashruth trial, 1936 (Box 17:830)
    - Leases of properties in Springfield, Massachusetts, 1938-1948 (Box 17:831)
    - Leases of properties in Springfield, Massachusetts, 1950-1952 (Box 17:832)
    - Leases of properties in Springfield, Massachusetts, 1953-1955 (Box 17:833)
    - Leases of properties in Springfield, Massachusetts, 1956-1958 (Box 17:834)
    - Leases of properties in Springfield, Massachusetts, 1960-1961 (Box 17:835)
    - Leases of properties in Springfield, Massachusetts, 1962-1964 (Box 17:836)
    - Leases of properties in Springfield, Massachusetts, 1965 (Box 17:837)
    - Leases of properties in Springfield, Massachusetts, 1966-1972 (Box 17:838)
    - Letters about mortgage on Kellogg Building and Bowles Lunch, Inc., 1949 (Box 17:839)
    - Mortgages, 1916-1938 (Box 17:840)
    - Offer to Raymond White for N.E. corner of Dwight and Hillman Streets in Springfield, Massachusetts, 1940 (Box 17:841)
    - Options on properties in Springfield, Masschusetts, 1915-1936 (Box 17:842)
    - Petition against the will of Henry L. Bowles, 1916-1938 (Box 17:843)
    - Power of attorney for David J. Nirenstein to act on the behalf of Nathan Nirenstein in the financial matters involving the Kellogg Buildings Realty Trust, 1956 (Box 17:844)
    - Receipt for Consolidated Chain Store stock purchased from Nathan Nirenstein, 1932 (Box 17:845)
    - Releases, 1928-1950 (Box 17:846)
    - Statement, Whitney Buildings, 1931 (Box 17:847)
    - Stock certificates, 1920-1973 (Box 17:848)
    - Widening of White Street in Springfield, Massachusetts, 1917-1921 (Box 17:849)
- Series IV: Financial Records, 1909-1983
  - Nirenstein National Realty Map Company
    - Financial statements, 1951-1973 (Box 18:850-870)
    - Master ledger, 1926-1927 (Volume 19)
    - Master ledger, 1928-19297 (Volume 20)
    - Master ledger, 1929-1930 (Volume 21)
    - Master ledger, 1935-1936 (Volume 22)
    - Master ledger, 1937-1938 (Volume 23)
    - Master ledger, 1938-1940 (Volume 24)
    - Master ledger, 1940-1943 (Volume 25)
    - Master ledger, 1943-1947 (Volume 26)
    - Master ledger, 1947-1951 (Volume 27)
    - Master ledger, 1951-1955 (Volume 28)
    - Master ledger, 1955-1960 (Volume 29)
    - Ledger, 1945-1949 (Volume 30)
    - Ledger, 1950-1953 (Volume 31)
    - General ledger, 1951 (Volume 32)
    - Ledger, 1953-1955 (Volume 33)
    - Ledger, 1955-1956 (Volume 34)
    - Accounts ledger, 1920-1923 (Volume 35)
    - Accounts ledger, 1924-1925 (Volume 36)
    - Accounts ledger, 1926-1927 (Volume 37)
    - Accounts ledger, 1928-1929 (Volume 38)
    - Accounts ledger, 1930-1931 (Volume 39)
    - Accounts ledger, 1932-1936 (Volume 40)
    - Accounts ledger, 1937-1941 (Volume 41)
    - Accounts ledger, 1942-1947 (Volume 42)
    - Accounts ledger, 1945-1948 (Volume 43)
    - Accounts ledger, 1946-1948 (Volume 44)
    - Accounts ledger, 1948-1952 (Volume 45)
    - Accounts ledger, 1953-1964 (Volume 46)
    - Accounts ledger, 1964-1971 (Volume 47)
    - Accounts receivable and payable, 1921-1954 (Volume 48)
    - Accounts receivable and payable, 1930-1940 (Volume 49)
    - Bill and payment ledger, 1940-1945 (Volume 50)
    - Shipments record ledger, 1945-1950 (Volume 51)
    - Shipments record ledger, 1945-1960 (Volume 52)
    - Shares of capital stock, undated (Volume 53)
    - Shares of capital stock, undated (Volume 54)
    - Petty cash book, 1977 (Volume 55)
  - Kellogg Building Realty Trust Company
    - Financial statements, 1936-1970 (Box 56:871-896)
    - Journal sheets, 1972-1970 (Box 57:897-899)
    - Cash disbursements, 1973-1976 (Box 57:900-902)
    - Journal, 1942-1956 (Volume 58)
    - Journal, 1949-1961 (Volume 59)
    - Journal, 1952-1955 (Volume 60)
    - Journal, 1953 (Volume 61)
    - Journal, 1980-1983 (Volume 62)
    - General accounts ledger, 1941-1945 (Volume 63)
    - Payroll book, 1951-1960 (Volume 64)
    - Rental records ledgers, undated, 1909-1929 (Volume 65-67)
    - Rental records, 1932-1955 (Volume 68)
    - Rental records, 1941-1947 (Volume 69)
    - Rental records, 1941-1956 (Volume 70)
    - Master ledger, 1947-1952 (Volume 71)
    - Master ledger, 1953-1956 (Volume 72)
    - Master ledger, 1967-1973 (Volume 73)
    - Master ledger, 1972-1976 (Volume 74)
  - Other Companies
    - Harrison Realty Corporation
      - Accounts ledger, 1941-1948 (Volume 75)
      - Accounts ledger, 1942-1948 (Volume 76)
      - Accounts ledger, 1948-1954 (Volume 77)
      - Accounts ledger, 1954-1960 (Volume 78)
    - Bowles Lunch, Inc.
      - Accounts ledger, 1931-1950 (Volume 79)
      - Accounts ledger, 1952-1954 (Volume 80)
      - Master ledger, 1947-1950 (Volume 81)
      - Master ledger, 1951-1956 (Volume 82)